<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Warrior Nun</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="ava_text">
    "Ava Silva is a character on Netflix\'s Warrior Nun. She is portrayed by Alba Baptista.\n\n"

    "She is tasting freedom for the first time in her young life after being liberated from "
    "an abusive orphanage and a prison of her mind and body. As a result, she wants to "
    "experience everything at once, and she can be reckless in her ambition.\n\n"

    "History\n"
    "Ava was a quadriplegia for twelve years, she was orphaned at the age of 7 when her mother "
    "died in a car accident she was in too, nothing is revealed about her father other than "
    "“he is not in the picture” and they didn't have any family in Spain, where she and her "
    "mother were on holiday. She was taken in by St. Michael Orphanage where it is shown in "
    "various flashbacks that she was mentally and verbally abused by Sister Frances.\n\n"

    "According Ava's file given by Sister Frances Ava committed suicide due to overdosing "
    "on painkillers, however, it is later revealed nearing the end of episode 4 that she "
    "was overdosed to death by Sister Frances who took care of her.\n\n"

    "During the first episode, A sister places the Halo artifact inside the corpse of "
    "19-year-old Ava to keep it protected. The holy relic resurrects Ava, and provides "
    "her with the abilities.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="mary_text">
    "Shotgun Mary is a character on Netflix\'s Warrior Nun. She is portrayed by Toya Turner.\n\n"

    "She is a woman loyal to the sisterhood more than the Church. She escaped family tragedy "
    "and was raised with religion but never really took to it fully. Naturally, she has a chip "
    "on her shoulder about loyalty. All the nuns know they can. count on Mary to have their "
    "backs.\n\n"

    "History\n"
    "Shotgun Mary revealed in Episode Isaiah 30:20-21 that her mother was in prison, serving "
    "a life sentence for murdering her abusive husband. She later finds the OCS, and she felt "
    "that it was her family. She was not a nun, also she did not take an oath to be a nun. "
    "At least she could be loyal not to her religion, but to Father Vincent.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="lilith_text">
    "Sister Lilith is a character on Netflix\'s Warrior Nun. She is portrayed by Lorena Andrea.\n\n"

    "She is born into an elite family, she is a legacy Nun and committed to her beliefs, "
    "which causes her to overstep and over-reach in her entitlement. \n\n"

    "History\n"
    "It's been known that her family has been serving the church for five generations as the "
    "Halo bearer.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="beatrice_text">
    "Sister Beatrice is a character on Netflix\'s Warrior Nun. She is portrayed by Kristina Tonteri-Young.\n\n"

    "She is a woman with a quiet Zen strength, Beatrice is a powerful Sister Warrior in her "
    "own right. The team’s resident strategist, Beatrice uses her reserved and intuitive "
    "nature to analyze everyone and everything around her.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="camila_text">
    "Sister Camila is a character on Netflix\'s Warrior Nun. She is portrayed by Olivia Delcán.\n\n"

    "Little is known of Camila however, she is a fierce fighter.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="which_nun_are_you">Which nun are you?</string>
    <string name="name_ava">Ava</string>
    <string name="name_mary">Shotgun Mary</string>
    <string name="name_lilith">Lilith</string>
    <string name="name_beatrice">Beatrice</string>
    <string name="name_camila">Camila</string>
    <string name="image_of_camila">Image of Camila</string>
    <string name="image_of_beatrice">Image of Beatrice</string>
    <string name="image_of_lilith">Image of Lilith</string>
    <string name="image_of_mary">Image of Mary</string>
    <string name="image_of_ava">Image of Ava</string>
    <string name="send_email">Send Nun an Email</string>
    <string name="image_of_nun">Image of Nun</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
</resources>